Hello everyone. You know me, my name is Ishiro Sugata. I'm currently seeking a new assistant.
In the age of discovery, Ferdinand Magellan found something significant. The southern route to
circumnavigate the globe. It was his crowning achievement that using his contemporary ship's
logs, he was able to prove that the earth was in fact round. This caused a ripple of panic to
course through the network of cartographers of the time. After all, it completely destroyed
their concept of the known world and their maps. I believe this type of discovery could happen
again now, if we could just somehow seek out this new world. On a side note, Magellan's
log also made note of footprints of giants near Patagonia. The possibility exists that whatever
he saw still lives on an island somewhere to this very day. What about you? Would you like
to be my new assistant? I can hear my heartbeat. How do you think you know?
go!
I can hear your heartbeat. How do you think you know?
Go!
It's a new world that came out! It's huge!
Get up!
Go!
I can't hear my heart, but I can't stop.
I can't hear my heart, but I can't hear my heart.
We're almost to summer vacation, Icarus, and it's getting way hot.
I think maybe we're going to have to buy an air conditioner.
Master, in looking around us, I think we need to sort out our living conditions first.
You might have a point.
The entire house went boom thanks to all those damn exploding panties.
Hey, I got it.
Why don't we just go stay at Sugata's place again?
That wasn't so bad.
Yo, Sugata!
Hmm?
Sorry to drop this on you out of nowhere, but do you mind if we stay here for a while?
Sure, knock yourselves out, you two.
Seriously? Score!
I can't guarantee your safety, though.
Huh?
Watch out! Behind you!
Bears are all over these parts this time of year.
You really have to watch your backs!
This sucks out loud.
I'm going to die a miserable death if I stay here.
No way!
You stay here and you'll just go sifting through my drawers looking for panties or some crap.
I already said you could stay at my place.
And get eaten by bears!
Yeah, whatever. You probably deserve it.
You are such a witch!
Childhood friends should help each other out, not wish death upon each other!
Promise not to steal my panties even if you're in my room with the perfect opportunity?
No.
Uh-huh.
Sure, you can count on me.
I don't buy it.
Isn't this some joyful banter?
What are we doing today?
Really?
Well, if that's the case, you're welcome to stay at my house.
What?
I'll be the sweetest host you could ever hope to have keep you.
Her place is huge, right?
People are always saying it's like the biggest one in town or something.
Her family are the big shots in Cerami!
And why not bring along Sahara and Sugata until your house gets fixed?
It'll be fun.
Now that sounds like the life.
We'll do it!
Excellent.
Well, that settles it then.
Why don't we get your things moved in?
I'll be heading back to my tent.
Dude, what's your problem, Sugata?
The mopey routine just isn't your style.
Moving up to the big time.
I am Mikako's father.
I invite you to stay with us for as long as you wish.
The Satsukitani family has been Cerami City's ruling clan since way back in the Edo period when it was just an in-town.
So that's what you meant when you called her family big shots?
That's about the shape of it.
You guys look freaked.
There's nothing to be scared about, I promise.
As long as you don't break any of the very specific rules, you'll be fine.
She's sorry, really, really sorry.
She's just a freaking idiot.
Please spare her life, sir.
Hey, no big deal.
What are you all doing standing around?
Hurry up and tend to our honored guests.
Yes, right away, sir.
What a spread!
Sir, please try some of this.
Perhaps you'd like some of mine, sir.
Have you noticed how they keep calling Sugata, sir?
Maybe, I don't know, cause like the Prez and him are all childhood friends or...
I don't know.
Would you like to take a walk?
What, are you serious?
I can't do this anymore.
I can't eat another thing.
Where's Master?
Ran off to take a bath.
Guess all that eating got him all messy.
Seriously?
He went to bathe?
Yeah, why?
Is that a problem?
No, but it could be the Satsukitani family has something called the Decapitation Bath.
It's open only to clan members.
He should be fine.
As long as Tomoki doesn't try to enter that particular bath.
Hello.
So you want to hop in with me?
I mean, I don't mind.
But it might be kind of weird.
No, it's cool!
You're actually much more forward than I would have given you credit for.
I mean, just walking in here the way you did.
N-no!
Sorry about this, though.
Gotta tell you something serious.
You really should hurry up and get the hell out of here.
Before someone kills you where you stand.
Uh-huh.
Oh, God.
Intruder alarm!
We have an intruder alarm!
There is an intruder in the Decapitation Bath!
After him!
There he is!
Get back here!
You really think you can get away?
These jerks are going to kill me!
Holy crap.
Mister, you gotta help!
Please don't let those dudes kill me!
I am sorry, young man.
But no matter how close of friends you are with my daughter,
our law on this matter is absolute.
Do it!
Tomaki!
Why is this happening?
The Decapitation Bath was originally a bath for our ancestor, a celestial maiden.
It was a place where she could cleanse her divine robe.
But after her passing, the bath was open to the public,
and Sarami was punished for doing so.
Earthquakes, famine, tornadoes.
The disasters never ceased until every single person who had visited the bath was decapitated.
Since that time,
our clan has had the honor of watching over this bath with utmost vigilance
in order to protect this fair town of Sarami.
Given his friendship with Mikako,
end his life quickly.
You can't do this!
Mikako, please make them stop!
I cannot.
Laws in the Satsukatane family are absolute.
Nothing I say would change their minds.
But Sugata,
you might be able to.
Stop this now!
If you take one more step, then I'll...
Oh, my young Sugata,
do you intend on defying the Satsukatane family?
This can't be happening.
No, please!
Please don't kill my friend!
Leave my way.
Take out my princess!
Stop this.
What are you doing to my master?
I asked you a question,
and I expect a satisfactory answer.
Icarus!
Stop it now!
I apologize for all the trouble we've caused you.
Forget it.
I'll overlook everything that happened today
on account of that young lady.
It appears she's not someone we should be taking lightly.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Understood, Master.
And don't worry about any of this.
I won't.
Mikako,
I am going to leave the rest of this matter in your hands.
Thank you.
Rise and shine!
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning to you two.
We're almost there,
so you better wake the heck up.
Where?
To the uninhabited island.
Huh?
What the hell is going on?
Wow, it's gorgeous.
This is a private island owned by my family.
I want you all to treat this place as your own home.
Just out of curiosity,
why'd you drag us to the middle of nowhere anyway?
Because a certain someone broke a sacred family law,
which has made it all a wee bit tense
staying back at the main house.
I would have felt awful tossing you out onto the street,
so I brought you here instead.
I hope that wasn't the wrong thing to do.
I could always take you back.
No, this is great.
Seriously, thanks.
You've gone really far out of your way for Tomoki,
haven't you?
Tomo,
you better show her some pretty serious gratitude.
Thank you, Prez.
You're welcome, Tomoki.
Well, since we're here,
let's go swimming.
Hold off for a second.
Don't underestimate uninhabited islands.
Before anything,
we need to secure a food source for our survival.
What?
Mikako said this is her family's island.
Isn't there some kind of cottage or bungalow?
Actually, we've got nothing at all.
And that's our situation.
So we can't afford to spend time sunning and swimming.
Why don't we leave finding the food to Icarus and Tomoki?
The rest of us will head out
to look for fresh drinking water.
Sure, sounds good.
Hey, Icarus.
Yes, Master?
Think maybe you should jump in the water
and catch us some bream or tuna or something tasty?
What do you say?
Yes, Master.
Make sure you catch some fat ones with a lot of meat on them.
Cool, I found a coconut crab.
Coconut crab sounds awesome.
I've always wanted to try one.
Here goes.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I don't want to eat you.
I don't.
This sucks balls.
On the verge of death because of some stupid crab.
Maybe we eat vegetarian this trip.
Man, I'm freaking starving.
Okay, clearly these mushrooms are a bad idea.
Oh, well.
No choice.
No way, sister.
Shut up!
Grandpa!
Holy crap.
Must have passed out after I eat that thing.
What the hell is this?
Save me!
Zahara!
Oh, my gosh.
No!
Zahara!
How did you get down here?
Are you okay?
I'm glad you're safe.
I was starting to get so worried about you.
What happened?
I thought you were with the others.
Where are they?
I don't know what happened to them.
Once we started running, we all got separated.
What's that?
That sound was chasing us, so we ran as fast as we could.
I'm scared, Tomaki.
We'll find a safe place to hide and sort out what's going on.
Calm down, Zahara.
I've got you.
We're gonna be fine.
When the sun comes up, we'll go search for everyone else.
Cool?
Cool.
When morning broke, we went looking for Prez, Sugata, and Icarus.
But one day turned into two, then turned into three, four, who knows how many.
We never found them.
But at night, we kept hearing the howl.
An awful, terrifying howl.
Oh, no.
What if they're all dead?
What if they got eaten by that horrible thing?
They'll be fine.
I just know it.
No way they'd go down so easy.
Yes, you're right.
I mean, I'm sure Prez would have called for help on her radio by now.
Yeah.
Check it out!
Wow, that's a pretty big catch for breakfast.
Just hand him over and I'll cook him up.
Cool.
Sounds good to me.
You want one bowl?
And so an entire month passed.
What do you think?
The two of us completely readjusted to life on the island.
So how I even started smiling again.
But just when I started thinking it wouldn't be all bad if things went on like this forever.
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I just started thinking about everybody else and got kind of sad.
It makes me wonder, what's going to happen if no one ever comes to rescue us?
Will we just live here forever?
I guess we'll have to make the most of the time we have together.
But with me here, at least you won't be lonely.
And I promise you now, you'll never be sad.
Thank you, Tomaki.
And you know, I'm thinking life wouldn't be near as depressing as it is now if we had kids.
You want to have kids?
You mean like now?
No, that's not what I was trying to say at all.
I meant to...
Um, Zahara.
I... It's okay, Tomaki.
We gotta get out of here.
Yeah.
Zahara!
Dammit, legs.
You have to move.
Do you hear me?
I said move!
Tomaki.
Don't worry about me.
I promise.
I'll be just fine.
I will.
Let her go, monster!
Let go of her, dammit!
Let her go!
Get your tentacles off her, you damn dirty beast!
I have returned with a fish, master.
I did not find many schools of tuna out here, so I crossed over to the southern hemisphere
to find this one.
Tomo, I think this is just seaweed and oysters.
It's what?
So they were just stuck all over Icarus like barnacles or something?
Yes.
As I walked along the ocean floor, all of that became stuck to me for some reason.
So what was that blood-curdling howl you let out?
And where are the others?
Master, do you wish for me to check for their life signs on my radar?
Yes, please do!
One moment.
Ha!
Now that's entertainment!
It's also your punishment for breaking the rules of my family.
And with that, I will exonerate him.
And I promise you now, you'll never be sad.
Thank you, Tomaki.
Oh, to be young and in love.
Well, I think it had more to do with the fact
that his life had recently been spared.
You're telling me all this crap?
All this happened because of something Tomaki did again?
Whoa, just calmed down, Sohara.
This whole thing was your fault, Tomo!
You're the biggest jerk on planet Earth!
Somebody help me!
It's like my house never even exploded.
What the hell?
Master, look over there.
Presents Icarus Breeding!
Hello!
Please accept this small token.
A gift from the entire Satsukatune family to you.
You may not have known this,
but strength counts for everything in my family.
And it looks like my father has grown rather attached to Icarus here.
Icarus Breeding!
We'll be right back.